Guide to the Gorham Munson Papers on the American Social Credit Movement and New Democracy, 1899 - 1969, bulk 1932 - 1945
Gorham Munson Papers on the American Social Credit Movement and New Democracy, 1899 - 1969, bulk 1932 - 1945
Munson's most revealing correspondence is with the slightly-known figures in the Social Credit movement. The chief exception to this is the correspondence with Ezra Pound, his father Homer Pound, James Laughlin IV and, to a lesser degree, William Carlos Williams. For England there is strong documentation in the letter files of the New English Weekly, Major C. H. Douglas, John Hargrave, Philip Mairet and Stanley Mott. For Canada the documentation lies more in published material Correspondence between Munson and R. Halliday Thompson is revealing of the difficulties of conducting an international Social Credit review, The Beacon of Winnipeg, which incorporated New Democracy in 1937-1939. For Australia and New Zealand there is published material and some correspondence such as that with Lilly Bierne.
For the United States the internal dynamics of the Social Credit movement are manifest in many files, especially those of Herbert Bruce Brougham, Allan R. Brown, Howard L. Buck, A. M. Edwards, Paul Hampden, Laurence Morris, W. A. Nyland, A. H. Spencer, Elliott Taylor, and Mrs. E. Sohier Welch. Congressional correspondents include Charles G. Binderup, Fred L. Crawford, T. Alan Goldsborough and Jerry F. Voorhis.
Correspondence will be found in four difference series in the Munson papers, arranged alphabetically in each by the name of the writer of the letter. In searching for material on any single individual the listings in all series should be consulted.
Collection Arrangement
The collection is arranged into the following series:
New Democracy Correspondence, 1932-1938: Office correspondence to and from staff: Gorham Munson, Herbert Bruce Brougham, W. A. Nyland, Lawrence and Paul Hampden. Occasional items outside the period that pertain to New Democracy and Social Credit are included.
ASCM Correspondence, 1938-1945: Office correspondence of staff, especially of Gorham Munson and Paul Hampden. Some items predate the founding of the American Social Credit Movement in October 1938.
Social Credit Subject File, 1932-1945: Materials from a succession of Social Credit organizations in which Munson was engaged, publications with which he had business (including New Democracy), and individuals associated with him. The series is divided by country. Contents of folders vary and include correspondence, memoranda, mimeographed and printed material. A few items stemming from the 1920s are included.
Munson Correspondence, 1922-1964: Scattered exchanges chiefly on topics other than Social Credit arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
Munson Writings, 1923-1963: Reviews of some of Munson's books. Copies of magazines in which his articles appeared and some tearsheets of his articles; the arrangement is alphabetical by title of the magazines. Manuscripts and typescripts, published and unpublished, are grouped roughly by period. Biographical information and photographs of Munson.
Pamphlets: 101 pamphlets dealing chiefly with Social Credit.
American Social Credit Movement Emblem: Emblem, 15 inches x 18 inches. A woodsman striking at the roots of a tree with lettering, American Social Credit Movement, green on white, wood.
Scrapbooks: Contain clippings on Social Credit news and related matters. The items are not ordered nor are particular scrapbooks limited to subjects. Complete inventory of scrapbooks is available as a PDF: http://www.wesleyan.edu/libr/schome/FAs/munson_scrapbooks.pdf
Periodicals: Social Credit periodicals from Australia, Canada, New Zealand, and the United Kingdom, and the United States. A total of 43 periodicals, short to full runs.
Books: Social Credit periodicals from Australia, Canada, New Zealand, and the United Kingdom, and the United States. A total of 43 periodicals, short to full runs.
Online Catalog Headings
These and related materials may be found under the following headings in online catalogs.
Munson, Gorham Bert, 1896-1969.; Pound, Ezra, 1885-1972.; Pound, Homer L. (Homer Loomis), 1858-1942.; Laughlin, James, 1914-1997.; Williams, William Carlos, 1883-1963.; Douglas, C. H. (Clifford Hugh), 1879-1952.; Hargrave, John, 1894-; Mairet, Philip, 1886-1975.; Mott, Stanley.; Bierne, Lilly.; Brougham, H. Bruce (Herbert Bruce), b. 1878.; Brown, Allan R.; Buck, Howard L.; Edwards, A. M.; Hampden, Paul.; Morris, Laurence.; Nyland, W. A.; Spencer, A. H.; Taylor, Elliott.; Welch, E. Sohier.; Binderup, Charles Gustav, 1873-1950.; Crawford, Fred L. (Fred Lewis), 1888-1957.; Goldsborough, T. Alan (Thomas Alan), 1877-1951.; Voorhis, Jerry, 1901-1984.; Social credit--History.; Finance--Great Britain.; Finance--United States.; Finance--Canada.; Finance--Australia.; Finance--New Zealand.; Social credit--Great Britain.; Social credit--United States.; Social credit--Canada.; Social credit--Australia.; Social credit--New Zealand.; Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.)--Alumni and alumnae.; New Democracy (New York, N.Y.); New English Weekly (London, England); Scrapbooks.; Pamphlets.
Related Material
Gorham Munson file, Vertical Files Collection, Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Gorham Munson and Elizabeth Delza Munson Papers [unprocessed], Special Collections & Archives, Wesleyan University
Ezra Pound Collection, Harry Ransom Humanities Research Center, University of Texas at Austin
Ezra Pound Papers, Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript LibraryYale University
Detailed Description of the Collection
- New Democracy Correspondence, 1932-1938
  Office correspondence to and from staff: Gorham Munson, Herbert Bruce Brougham, W. A. Nyland, Lawrence and Paul Hampden. Occasional items outside the period that pertain to New Democracy and Social Credit are included.
  Numbers in parentheses indicate number of letters to and from Munson. For example, (9/12) means that the folder contains 9 letters to Munson, and 12 letters from Munson.
  - A- General, 1935-1936 (9/12) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Aberhart, William, 1936-1938 (0/2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Addis, Dr. T., 1933-1934 (4/1) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agee, James, 1935 (1/1) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Allen, Hervey, 1933-1935 (4/4) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Altman, Irving B., 1937-1938 (3/1) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Atter, Ernest J., 1936-1937 (11/13) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - B- General, 1933-1937 (49/45) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Barber, Joseph, 1935 (2/1) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bardsley, W. L., 1934-1936 (12/6) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Barnes, Harry Elmer, 1936 (2/0) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bates, Eda T., 1935-1938 (15/8) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Beall, Clarkson J., 1938 (2/2) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bell, C. Frederick, 1935 (6/9) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bell, T. S., 1935-1938 (13/23) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bennett, J. D., 1935 (2/10) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bergen, Vaughn, 1936-1938 (10/8) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Binderup, Charles (M. C.), 1937 (2/2) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bingham, Alfred, 1937 (2/2) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Boyd, Ernest, 1934-1935 (1/2) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bragdon, Claude, 1934-1935 (4/2) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Brandt, Zelma Corning, 1935-1936 (7/9) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Brenton, Arthur, 1933-1936 (2/7) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Brickhouse, T. S., 1937 (5/6) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Brockman, J. B., 1935-1937 (4/7) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Brougham, Herbert Bruce, 1933-1935 (23/11) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Browder, Earl, 1937-1938 (1/5) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Brown, Allan, R., 1934-1938 (12/29) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Buck, Howard L., 1935-1938 (31/33) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Buck, Lillian G., 1935-1938 (25/19) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Buckley, Mary, 1935-1938 (12/20) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Burke, Kenneth, 1934-1937 (3/1) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Burn, D. W. M., 1935 (5/3) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - C - General, 1933-1937 (44/47) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Carrick, Lynn, 1935 (14/12) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Chamberlain, John, 1935? (1/0) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Chaplin, Charles, 1934 (0/1) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Chase, Stuart, 1933-1939 (1/2) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Clark, Wallace, 1937-1938 (3/4) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Cliffe, Sydney H., 1935-1938 (7/8) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Corr, J. Wilfred, 1935 (19/16) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Corr, J. Wilfred, 1936-1938 (32/32) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Cosgrave, John O'Hara, 1934-1936 (12/8) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Coward, Mrs. Thomas R., 1935-1936 (2/8) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - D - General, 1934-1938 (11/10) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Davidson, Donald, 1935-1937 (2/1) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Dekker, H. C., 1935-1938 (11/12) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - DeKruif, Paul, 1933-1938 (1/4) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Denny, George, 1935 (1/1) (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Dick, Samuel M., 1936 (5/3) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Dobree, Bonamy, 1935 (2/1) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Dougherty, J. Hampton, 1937-1938 (0/4) (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Douglas, Major C. H., 1933 (2/9) (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Douglas, Major C. H., 1934 (1/0) (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Douglas, Major C. H., 1933-1938 (10/6) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Dow, Richard S., 1935-1938 (38/32) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - E - General (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1935 (3/5) (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1935 (7/10) (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1936 (21/13) (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1936 (21/10) (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1937 (22/13) (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1937 (8/6) (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1938 (15/5) (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Eliot, T. S., 1935 (0/1) (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - F - General, 1934-1938 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Farrell, James T., 1934 (1/1) (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Fishburne, Mary Hamilton, 1936-1938 (12/15) (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Fitzgerald, James, 1935-1937 (18/10) (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Fletcher, Joseph F., 1934-1936 (3/5) (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Fletcher, J. G., 1934-1935 (3/2) (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Franklin, J. A., 1936-1937 (7/3) (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - G - General, 1934-1936 (18/23) (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Gandy, W. Owen, 1935-1938 (49/36) (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Goldsborough, T. Alan (M. C.), 1935 (3/6) (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Goldsborough, T. Alan (M. C.), 1936 (6/7) (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Goldsborough, T. Alan (M. C.), 1937 (20/18) (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Goldsborough, T. Alan (M. C.), 1938-1939 (7/10) (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Grant, Blanche B., 1934-1936 (23/26) (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Gray, R. S., 1935 (16/11) (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Gregory, Horace, 1933 (2/0) (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Grieve, C. M., 1928 (1/0) (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Gwathmey, Allan, 1935-1937 (12/15) (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - H - General, 1934-1938 (28/41) (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Haight, Raymond L., 1935-1937 (14/20) (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Hampden, Paul, 1935-1938 (15/8) (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Hampden, Walter, 1934-1936 (1/5) (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Hardy, Harry, 1935-1936 (0/5) (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Hare, Meredith (Mrs.), 1934-1937 (3/12) (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Hargrave, John, 1934 (5/1) (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Hargrave, John, 1935 (9/11) (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Hargrave, John, 1937 (3/4) (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Hargrave, John, 1938 (6/4) (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Hargrave, John, 1939 (15/9) (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Harter, Thomas J., 1935-1938 (17/14) (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Harvey, Edward S., 1934-1937 (24/27) (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Haugen, Emil, 1937-1938 (5/12) (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Highberger, William W., 1936-1938 (6/6) (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Hillman, Elizabeth, 1935 (8/7) (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Holter, Elizabeth Sage, 1935-1938 (7/9) (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Horton, Walter M., 1935-1936 (6/8) (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Hyatt, Miles, 1936-1937 (4/4) (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - I - General, 1934-1938 (5/5) (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - J - General, 1934-1935 (2/3) (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Jaeger, Lloyd, 1938 (3/2) (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Jeffrey, R. L., 1937 (3/2) (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Johnson, Dallas D., 1934-1938 (30/34) (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - K - General, 1934-1938 (30/34) (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Keeping, Charles, 1938 (8/9) (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Kerslake, C. V., 1933-1936 (17/7) (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - L - General, 1933-1938 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Larkin, J. Crate, 1934-1938 (26/44) (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Laughlin, James IV, 1934-1935 (17/17) (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Laughlin, James IV, 1936 (25/31) (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Laughlin, James IV, 1937 (10/9) (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Laughlin, James IV, 1938-1939 (13/10) (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Lentz, Nicholas, 1934-1938 (31/22) (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Lewis, Samuel L., 1935-1938 (40/21) (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Liberal Press, 1934-1935 (0/9) (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Luntz, Charles E., 1934-1938 (19/22) (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - M - General, 1933-1938 (34/36) (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - McCall, T. D., 1935 (9/8) (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - MacKenzie, Duncan, 1938 (1/2) (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Mack, Harold L., 1934-1936 (27/34) (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - MacLeish, Archibald, 1935-1940 (11/9) (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Mairet, Philip, 1934-1935 (3/2) (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Mansfield, Margery, 1936-1937 (4/2) (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Martin, Horace J., 1935-1937 (8/7) (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Mason, C. W., 1935-1937 (5/7) (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Massonneau, Reginald C., 1935-1938 (8/15) (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Masten, Stewart M., 1935-1938 (7/4) (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Mengas, Frank H., 1935 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Miller, Louis T., 1934-1936 (9/13) (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Morris, Lawrence, 1934-1936 (19/9) (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - N - General, 1934-1938 (15/28) (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Norman, Dorothy, undated (0/1) (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Nott, Stanley, 1934-1938 (37/26) (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Nyland, W. A., 1933-1936 (37/24) (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - O - General, 1935-1936 (2/6) (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - O'Donnell, George Marion, 1936-1937 (5/2) (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Orage, A. R., 1932 (1/0) (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Overholser, Willis A., 1938 (3/3) (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Overstreet, H. A., 1933-1938 (5/11) (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - P - General, 1934-1938 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Paterson, Isabel, 1936 (0/3) (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Patman, Wright (M. C.), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Pendill, Caludius G., 1935 (8/8) (Box 6, Folder 147)
  - Pinchot, Amos, 1934-1935 (1/2) (Box 6, Folder 148)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1933 (17/0) (Box 6, Folder 149)
  - Pound, Ezra, January 1934-September 1934 (19/2) (Box 6, Folder 150)
  - Pound, Ezra, October 1934-December 1934 (6/1) (Box 6, Folder 151)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1934 (6/0) (Box 6, Folder 152)
  - Pound, Ezra, January 1935-May 1935 (11/3) (Box 6, Folder 153)
  - Pound, Ezra, June 1935-December 1935 (8/4) (Box 6, Folder 154)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1935 (7/9) (Box 6, Folder 155)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1936 (13/8) (Box 6, Folder 156)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1937 (5/4) (Box 6, Folder 157)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1938 (3/0) (Box 6, Folder 158)
  - Pound, Ezra, 1939-1940 (5/5) (Box 6, Folder 159)
  - Pound, Ezra, circa 1932-1940 (20/0) (Box 6, Folder 160)
  - Pound, Homer, 1935-1939 (7/4) (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Powell, G. F., 1937-1938 (7/8) (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - R - General, 1934-1938 (11/7) (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Riedel, C. G., 1935-1936 (7/6) (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Riordan, John, 1935-1938 (9/10) (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Robinson, Boardman, 1934-1938 (6/10) (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Rose, William, 1935-1936 (10/13) (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Rowntree, Bernard, 1935-1937 (13/12) (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Ryder, David Warren, 1933-1937 (29/27) (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - S - General, 1933-1938 (20/26) (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Sayers, Michael, 1936 (8/3) (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Schwarzenbach, Marguerite, 1935-1938 (7/19) (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Scott, John G., 1935-1936 (10/11) (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Seldes, Gilbert, 1935 (4/9) (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Serra, W. C., 1935-1936 (4/4) (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Simons, H., 1938 (1/0) (Box 7, Folder 176)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1936-1937 (1/3) (Box 7, Folder 177)
  - Skorstad, J. B., 1935-1938 (5/7) (Box 7, Folder 178)
  - Smith, Chard Powers, 1937 (2/2) (Box 7, Folder 179)
  - Stanton, F. L., 1934-1935 (5/3) (Box 7, Folder 180)
  - Steele, Thea B., 1935-1936 (10/22) (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Stieglitz, Alfred, 1935 (1/0) (Box 7, Folder 182)
  - T - General, 1933-1937 (16/28) (Box 7, Folder 183)
  - Taylor, Elliott, 1935-1938 (Box 7, Folder 184)
  - Taylor, Harcourt M., 1935-1938 (27/16) (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - Thomas, Lowell, 1938 (1/0) (Box 7, Folder 186)
  - Thomas, Norman, 1934-1939 (8/7) (Box 7, Folder 187)
  - Thomason, Oliver M., 1936 (4/4) (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1936 (2/3) (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Thompson, R. Halliday, 1937-1938 (32/55) (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Toomer, Jean, 1935-1938 (3/0) (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - U, V - General, 1934-1935 (1/2) (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Untermeyer, Jean Starr, 1936 (2/0) (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Voorhis, Jerry F. (M. C.), 1937 (3/4) (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - W - General, 1933-1938 (20/19) (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Welch, Mrs. E. Sohier, 1934-1936 (65/66) (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Welch, Mrs. E. Sohier, 1937 (55/48) (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Welch, Mrs. E. Sohier, 1938 (26/26) (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - Whiteman, Luther, 1933-1935 (51/43) (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Whiteman, Luther, 1936-1938 (34/38) (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1933 (2/0) (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1934 (5/1) (Box 8, Folder 202)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1935 (4/7) (Box 8, Folder 203)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1936 (10/9) (Box 8, Folder 204)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1937-1938 (2/2) (Box 8, Folder 205)
  - Williams, William Carlos, 1939 (2/2) (Box 8, Folder 206)
  - Wilson, Lucius E., 1936 (3/3) (Box 8, Folder 207)
  - Winchester, Harold P., 1934-1936 (28/30) (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Woodward, W. E., 1935 (1/0) (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - X, Y, Z - General (2/2) (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Zanettin, R. J., 1938 (Box 8, Folder 211)
- American Social Credit Movement Correspondence, 1938-1945
  Office correspondence of staff, especially of Gorham Munson and Paul Hampden. Some items predate the founding of the American Social Credit Movement in October 1938.
  - Allen, Stanley F., 1943 (4/0) (Box 9)
  - Altman, Irving, 1939-1940 (3/6) (Box 9)
  - Anderson, Paul E., 1939-1941, 1943 (10/5) (Box 9)
  - B - General, 1939-1942 (Box 9)
  - Baldwin, Roger, 1942 (4/3) (Box 9)
  - Beard, Charles, 1939 (2/1) (Box 9)
  - Bearss, Louise, 1939 (2/4) (Box 9)
  - Beirne, Lilly, 1941-1942 (17/16) (Box 9)
  - Belikoff, Morris, 1941-1942 (7/6) (Box 9)
  - Bell, Daniel, 1942 (1/0) (Box 9)
  - Bell, T. S., 1939-1941 (2/5) (Box 9)
  - Benet, William Rose, 1942 (1/0) (Box 9)
  - Benson, Ira, 1941 (6/4) (Box 9)
  - Bergen, Vaughn, 1940-1942 (4/7) (Box 9)
  - Binderup, Charles G. (M. C.), 1939 (1/3) (Box 9)
  - Binzel, Alma L., 1939 (3/4) (Box 9)
  - Bishop, A. S., 1944 (3/0) (Box 9)
  - Blackmore, John (M. P.), 1940-1941 (4/3) (Box 9)
  - Brickhouse, T. S., 1938-1940 (3/4) (Box 9)
  - Brockman, J. B., 1938-1942 (6/4) (Box 9)
  - Buck, Howard, 1938-1942 (14/12) (Box 9)
  - Buck, Lillian, 1939-1943 (46/25) (Box 9)
  - Burn, D. W. M., 1938-1943 (12/5) (Box 9)
  - Burnham, Philip, 1941 (3/4) (Box 9)
  - Burton, Jean, 1940-1941 (1/3) (Box 9)
  - Butchart, Montgomery, 1939 (3/3) (Box 9)
  - Byrnes, L. D., 1939-1941 (2/4) (Box 9)
  - C - General, 1939-1942 (Box 9)
  - Calverton, V. F., 1939 (2/2) (Box 9)
  - Christensen, George C., 1939 (13/1) (Box 9)
  - Clark, Willace, 1940-1941 (11/6) (Box 9)
  - Clyma, Cecil, 1939-1940 (12/9) (Box 9)
  - Colbourne, Maurice, 1939-1942 (9/11) (Box 9)
  - Collins, Seward, 1942 (1/0) (Box 9)
  - Conant, Luther Jr., 1942 (Box 9)
  - Corey, Lewis, 1940 (Box 9)
  - Corr, J. Wilfred, 1938-1939 (Box 9)
  - Cosgrave, John O'Hara, 1940-1941 (3/2) (Box 9)
  - Cousens, Hilderic, 1939 (3/2) (Box 9)
  - Coward, Vanessa, 1939-1941 (3/6) (Box 9)
  - Crawford, Fred L. (M. C.), 1938-1942 (4/13) (Box 9)
  - Cromwell, James H. R., 1939-1940 (2/4) (Box 9)
  - D - General, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
  - Dekker, H. C., 1938-1942 (28/17) (Box 10)
  - Dies, Martin (M. C.), 1942-1943 (0/5) (Box 10)
  - Distin, Wilber, 1945-1946 (5/0) (Box 10)
  - Douglas, Major C. H., 1940 (2/2) (Box 10)
  - Dow, Richard S., 1940 (4/4) (Box 10)
  - E - General, 1939-1943 (Box 10)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1939 (4/0) (Box 10)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1939 (34/26) (Box 10)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1940 (20/10) (Box 10)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1940 (32/11) (Box 10)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1941 (18/7) (Box 10)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1941 (42/5) (Box 10)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1942 (22/3) (Box 10)
  - Edwards, A. M., 1942 (7/2) (Box 10)
  - Epstein, Benjamin R., 1942 (3/2) (Box 10)
  - Estoric, Eric, 1939-1940 (3/2) (Box 10)
  - F - General, 1938-1945 (Box 10)
  - G - General, 1942 (Box 10)
  - Gagnon, Paul, 1938-1940 (5/5) (Box 10)
  - Gallagher, James H., 1942 (2/2) (Box 10)
  - Gandy, W. Owen, 1938-1939 (1/3) (Box 10)
  - Garrett, Eileen, 1943 (1/0) (Box 10)
  - Gibson, David J., 1939 (2/2) (Box 10)
  - Goldsborough, T. Alan (M. C.), 1941-1942 (Box 10)
  - Gray, R. S., 1938 (2/1) (Box 10)
  - Gwathmey, Allan T., 1938-1942 (14/14) (Box 10)
  - H - General, 1938-1943 (Box 11)
  - Hacker, Louis, 1941 (1/0) (Box 11)
  - Hagen, Harold C. (M. C.), 1939-1943 (9/5) (Box 11)
  - Halliday, M. E., 1941 (3/5) (Box 11)
  - Hamilton, Mary F., 1940 (3/2) (Box 11)
  - Hampden, Paul, 1938-1939 (18/27) (Box 11)
  - Hampden, Paul, 1940 (33/6) (Box 11)
  - Hampden, Paul, 1940 (29/22) (Box 11)
  - Hampden, Paul, 1941-1943 (17/7) (Box 11)
  - Hampden, Walter, 1945 (2/0) (Box 11)
  - Hargrave, John, 1940 (9/12) (Box 11)
  - Hargrave, John, 1941 (7/5) (Box 11)
  - Hargrave, John, 1942-1943 (4/3) (Box 11)
  - Harter, T. J., 1938-1942 (26/25) (Box 11)
  - Harvey, Edward F., 1938-1942 (8/5) (Box 11)
  - Haugen, Emil, 1940-1942 (4/2) (Box 11)
  - Hawes, Harriet B., 1939-1942 (8/7) (Box 11)
  - Heinlein, Robert A., 1939-1941 (7/4) (Box 11)
  - Hickling, George, 1940-1943 (3/7) (Box 11)
  - Highberger, William W., 1938-1942 (11/14) (Box 11)
  - Hillyard, Sydney, 1939-1942 (17/14) (Box 11)
  - Hoag, C. G., 1940-1941 (3/2) (Box 11)
  - Hogan, John, 1938-1939 (5/5) (Box 11)
  - Holmes, Emil E., 1938-1939 (2/2) (Box 11)
  - Holmes, John Haynes, 1941-1942 (1/1) (Box 11)
  - Holmes, Thomas J., 1943 (5/0) (Box 11)
  - Horton, Walter M., 1939-1940 (4/6) (Box 11)
  - I - General, 1940, 1943 (Box 11)
  - J - General, 1940-1941, 1943 (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Dallas D., 1938-1940 (16/22) (Box 11)
  - Jukes, Major A. H., 1941-1943 (8/6) (Box 11)
  - K - General, 1939-1943 (Box 11)
  - Kennedy, T., 1938-1939 (1/3) (Box 12)
  - Kyle, J. Scott, 1938-1939 (3/3) (Box 12)
  - L - General, 1939-1945 (Box 12)
  - LaFarge, Christopher, 1941 (1/1) (Box 12)
  - Lamont, Corliss, 1942 (1/0) (Box 12)
  - Larkin, J. Crate, 1938-1939 (4/5) (Box 12)
  - Laughlin, James IV, 1939 (4/4) (Box 12)
  - Laughlin, James IV, 1940 (3/6) (Box 12)
  - Laughlin, James IV, 1941-1942 (3/4) (Box 12)
  - LeClere, Mary L, 1941-1942 (13/7) (Box 12)
  - L'Engle, Lucy, 1938-1939 (2/3) (Box 12)
  - Lentz, Nicholas, 1938-1939 (14/17) (Box 12)
  - Lentz, Nicholas, 1940 (14/12) (Box 12)
  - Lentz, Nicholas, 1941-1943 (14/10) (Box 12)
  - Lerner, Max, 1943 (1/1) (Box 12)
  - Lewis, Edith, 1940-1942 (6/6) (Box 12)
  - Lewis, Samuel L., 1938-1939 (5/6) (Box 12)
  - Locke, Alain, 1942 (1/0) (Box 12)
  - Lundquist, Edwin D., 1938-1942 (8/9) (Box 12)
  - Luntz, C. E., 1938-1941 (8/13) (Box 12)
  - M - General, 1939-1943 (Box 12)
  - MacKenzie, Duncan, 1938-1942 (12/8) (Box 12)
  - Mairet, Philip, 1938-1945 (7/18) (Box 12)
  - Marsten,Howard E., 1945 (1/1) (Box 12)
  - Martin, Horace J., 1942-1943 (7/3) (Box 12)
  - Masten, Stuart, 1938-1940 (15/10) (Box 12)
  - Miller, Wesley C., 1939-1941 (11/17) (Box 12)
  - Morrison, Theodore, 1938-1940 (3/0) (Box 12)
  - Moseley, Sydney A., 1943 (0/3) (Box 12)
  - N - General, 1938-1939 (Box 12)
  - Nott, Stanley, 1940 (6/5) (Box 12)
  - O - General, 1938, 1942, 1945 (Box 12)
  - P - General, 1938-1945 (Box 12)